<docs>
	<members name="specresponsesigned">
		<SpecResponseSigned>
			<summary>
				This class rapresent an immutable message that allow save all important information for a response that a replica must create
				before that this response to client, this message is signed with private key of the replica. 
			</summary>
		</SpecResponseSigned>
		<SpecResponseSignedC>
			<summary>
				This constructor create an instance of this class that allow send this message a client in response to request, this constructor is 
				initial and this allow you can be create a final spec-response-signed with all neccesary information.
			</summary>
			<param name="view">This parameter represent the actual view that the system contains.</param>
			<param name="sequenceNumber">This parameter represent the sequence number that is associated to this response, this sequence number is equal to sequence number in order-req where order-req is a 
			request.</param>
			<param name="digestResponse">This parameter represent the digest for this message.</param>
			<param name="client">This parameter represent the reference to client that the replica must responsea.</param>
			<param name="timestamp">
				This parameter represent timestamp that client has inserted inside request message
				when this has send request message.</param> 

		</SpecResponseSignedC>
		<SpecResponseSignedC2>
			<summary>
				Create an instance of this class that allow send this message a client in response to request.
			</summary>
			<param name="old">This parameter represent the old spec response signed.</param>
			<param name="history">This parameter represent all history that a replica contains.</param>
		 

		</SpecResponseSignedC2>
		<View>
			<summary>
				This property represent the actual view of the system.
			</summary>
		</View>
		<SequenceNumber>
			<summary>
				This property represent the sequence number that the request for this response contains.
			</summary>
		</SequenceNumber>
		<Client>
			<summary>
				This property is a reference to actor client that make this request  <see cref="IActorRef"></see>.
			</summary>
		</Client>
		<Timestamp>
			<summary>
				This property represent the timestamp that client has inserted inside request message 
				when this has send request message <see cref="Request{T}"></see>.
			</summary>
		</Timestamp>
		<History>
			<summary>
				This property is a <see cref="List{OrderReq}"></see> that contains all <see cref="OrderReq"></see> that this replica has run so far.
			</summary>
		</History>
		<DigestResponse>
			<summary>
				This property represent digest for this response, normally is used <see cref="SHA512"></see>.
			</summary>
		</DigestResponse>
</members>
</docs>
